To Restore Harmony, The Bands Must Battle!
My Little Pony - Equestria Girls - Rainbow Rocks is a family,
animation, music film directed by Jayson Thiessen.
Music rules and rainbows rock as Twilight Sparkle and pals compete for the
top spot in the Canterlot High "Mane Event" talent show.
The girls must rock their way to the top, and outshine rival Adagio Dazzle and
her band The Dazzlings, to restore harmony back to Canterlot High.
Twilight Sparkle (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Applejack / Rainbow Dash (voice), played by Ashleigh Ball.
Pinkie Pie / Fluttershy (voice), played by Andrea Libman.
Rarity / Vice Principal Luna / Photo Finish
(voice), played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Spike (voice), played by Cathy Weseluck.
Sunset Shimmer (voice) / Twilight Sparkle (singing
voice), played by Rebecca Shoichet.
My Little Pony: Equestria Girls (or simply Equestria Girls) is a fashion doll and media franchise launched in 2013
by American toy company Hasbro, as a spin-off of the 2010 relaunch of the My Little Pony toy line.
The franchise features anthropomorphized versions of characters from the Friendship Is Magic television series; as with My Little Pony,
the dolls have colorful bodies and hair, while incorporating their pony counterparts' "cutie marks" in their clothing.
Along with licensed merchandise, Hasbro (through its subsidiary Allspark Animation) has comissioned several animated works
to accompany the doll line, including four films, eight television specials, and multiple short-form series.
The setting of Equestria Girls is established as a parallel universe to the main world of Equestria in the 2010 incarnation of My Little Pony, populated by humanoid
versions of the "Mane Six" and other characters; Hasbro's marketing materials describe them as "full-time students and part-time magical pony girls".
The film explores themes of high school, friendship, equestria girls.